Feeling hungry?
饿了？
How about some worms with your spaghetti?
在你的意大利面里加些虫子怎么样？
Perhaps some ground cricket to sprinkle on your pizza?
或许在你的披萨上撒上些磨碎的蟋蟀？
Or maybe just a good old bug burger?
又或者来一个经典的虫子汉堡？
While the idea of eating insects disgusts many, don‘t be surprised if you find creepy-crawlies on your own plate before long.
虽然吃昆虫的想法让很多人反感，但如果不久后你在自己的盘子里发现爬虫，也别感到惊讶。
Why?
为什么呢？
Because insects could hold the key to the challenge of feeding the world’s growing population.
因为昆虫可能是解决全球不断增长的人口的食物供应这一挑战的关键。
With the number of humans on the planet expected to reach 9 billion by 2050, the search is on for alternative sources of protein beyond the traditional meat and fish.
预计到2050年，地球上的人口数量将达到90亿，人们正在寻找除了传统的肉类和鱼类之外的蛋白质替代来源。
Insects are not only high in protein, but also minerals and amino acids, according to Shami Radia, co-founder of Grub, a company which sells edible bugs.
据销售可食用昆虫的公司Grub的联合创始人沙米·拉迪亚说，昆虫不仅富含蛋白质，还含有矿物质和氨基酸。
“Insects are the original superfood,” says Radia.
拉迪亚说：“昆虫是创新的超级食物。”
Environmentally, insects produce less greenhouse gas, use less water and take up less farmland than conventional livestock farming, meaning they have a smaller impact on the planet.
从环境角度来看，与传统的畜牧业相比，昆虫产生的温室气体更少，用水更少，占用的农田也更少，这意味着它们对地球的影响更小。
So if they‘re good for the environment and good for you, why aren’t we eating insects?
那么，如果昆虫对环境有益，对我们也有益，为什么我们还不吃昆虫呢？
In fact, in many places we already are.
事实上，在很多地方人们已经在吃了。
It‘s estimated that two billion people around the world eat insects as part of their diet.
据估计，全世界有20亿人把昆虫作为他们饮食的一部分。
But most Western nations have not yet adopted the practice.
但大多数西方国家还没有接受这种做法。
It’s the “yuck factor” that stops them from eating bugs, according to the Waste and Resources Action Programme.
根据废物及资源行动计划的说法，是“令人厌恶的因素”阻止了他们吃昆虫。
People in the West generally view insects as unclean and carriers of disease.
西方人通常认为昆虫不干净，是疾病的携带者。
They‘re seen as pests: they destroy crops, ruin furniture and live in dirty places.
它们被视为是害虫：它们破坏庄稼，毁坏家具，还生活在肮脏的地方。
But perhaps attitudes are slowly shifting.
但或许人们的态度正在慢慢改变。
Certain types of insects are becoming more palatable to consumers, such as locusts and grasshoppers.
某些种类的昆虫对消费者来说变得更可口了，比如蝗虫和蚱蜢。
Nick Cooper sells insects as food through his UK company Crunchy Critters, and has seen a sales growth rate of 25% year on year.
尼克·库珀通过他在英国的公司Crunchy Critters（松脆的小动物）销售昆虫食品，并且销售额逐年增长25%。
He believes young people are more open to eating insects.
他认为年轻人对吃昆虫持更开放的态度。
Shami Radia believes that munching bugs will one day become as popular as eating sushi.
沙米·拉迪亚认为，有一天吃虫子会像吃寿司一样受欢迎。
“Behaviour can be changed,” he says.
他说：“行为是可以改变的。
“Prawns are ugly and taste delicious and there‘s no reason why eating insects can’t be normalised.”
虾长得很丑，但味道鲜美，没有理由不能让吃昆虫变得正常化。”